ReLIFE Experiment Contract
（夜明(よあけ)）
我々 リライフ研究所は—
ReLIFE Laboratory is an organization
that is developing a program
社会からドロップアウトした
いわゆるニートを対象に—
to rehabilitate people who have dropped out
of society: your so-called NEETs.
社会復帰のためのプログラムを
検証している組織です
For a year starting this spring,
（夜明）この春から １年間
高校生になって—
we want you to be a student,
高校に行っていただきたいんです
and go back to high school!
I've come too far to turn back!
（海崎(かいざき)）ここまで来たら
なるようになれだ
Fine, you're on!
I'll do this ReLIFE thing!
やってやろうじゃねえか
リライフ！
〜♪
Communication Skills: Zero
I can't handle waking up this early.
（海崎）早起き マジでつらい
Based on yesterday's tests,
（天津(あまつ)）昨日のテストの結果
３年３組 １学期の委員長は—
the 3-3 class reps for the first term are:
男子 大神(おおが)君
女子 日代(ひしろ)さんに決まりました
Oga-kun for the boys,
and Hishiro-san for the girls.
（大神･日代）
よろしくお願いします
Great to be working with you all!
I look forward to working with you all.
ぜんっぶ 赤点
I failed all of them!
I don't believe Oga.
大神 すげえ
He's actually smart.
頭よかったんだな
チャラいのに
With these two leading you,
I hope you have a fun first term.
（天津）今学期は
この２人を中心に—
But he's so showy.
楽しく
やっていきましょう
狩生(かりう)… さん？
Kariu-san?
What's up with her? She looks furious.
（海崎）何だ？ すっげえ不機嫌
（大神）でも 今年は
学年トップの日代さんと—
But this year, she's in the same class as
Hishiro-san, the top scorer in our grade.
同じクラスになってしまった
そりゃ 休んでもられないし
燃えますよってわけ
So she's all fired up now
and couldn't call in sick.
Oh, she must be mad
she didn't top the class.
（海崎）そっか
トップになれなかったから
Pleasure working with ya, Hishiro-san.
（大神）よろしくね 日代さん
（日代）はい
Likewise.
That's it for homeroom.
ホームルームは以上
シルバーピンは 後で
職員室 取りに来て
Drop by the staff room later
to pick up your silver pins.
（大神）はーい
（日代）はい
Okay.
（女子生徒）先生
（天津）ん？
Sensei!
（大神）残念だったな 狩生
（海崎）なっ…
Too bad, huh, Kariu?
（海崎）何 追い打ちかけてんだよ
空気読めよ 大神
Why're you rubbing salt into her wound?
Get a clue, Oga!
But, well, you did have a cold.
でも 風邪 引いてたし
次は 万全で勝負できるといいな
Hope you can take her on
at full strength next time.
Whatever. It was all my fault,
including my failure to take care of myself.
（狩生）別に
体調管理も含めて
自己責任だし—
I don't wanna use the cold as an excuse.
風邪を言い訳にしたくない
あたしのほうが下だった
それだけ
I just wasn't as good as her.
That's all.
ストイックだなあ
かわいげない
You're so indifferent. Not cute.
（海崎）大神 その辺にしとけ
Knock it off already, Oga.
Yeah, yeah, I'm not cute!
どうせ かわいげないわよ！
I bet you're glad you don't
have to work with me anymore!
よかったね！ 委員長の相手
あたしじゃなくなって
Nah...
いや…
そんなこと 思ってないけど
I don't think that.
What's with the persecution complex?
何で そんな被害妄想してんの？
うっ… もういい この話！
Just drop it already.
What the heck?
I was trying to cheer you up!
何だよ 慰めたんだろ
そういうの 上から言われても
超微妙！
By talking down to me? Ugh.
んん？
これは もしや…
Oh? Could it be?
Why are you so pissed?
何 イライラしてんだよ
んん？
これは もしや…
（狩生）うるさい！
（天津）あっ そうだ
Shut up!
Oh, I almost forgot. About the tests...
（天津）テストのことですが
（大神･海崎）おっ
いつもどおり １つでも
赤点のある人は 再テストだからね
As always, if you failed even one,
you're going to take make-ups.
And you'll keep taking them
until you score higher than 50.
50点以上 取れるまで
何度でもやるわよ
１回で受かるように
きちんと勉強すること
Study hard so you pass the first time.
F-Fifty or more on all of them?!
（海崎）ぜっ 全部 50点以上…
Endless make-ups!
エンドレス再試！
What? You failed one, Kaizaki?
何？ 海崎 赤点あったの？
あったも何も 全部ですけど
Not "one." All of them.
Wow, people like that actually exist?
マジでいるんだ そういう人
By the way, which was the worst?
（大神）
ちなみに 一番悪かったのは？
Math. I got a four.
（海崎）数学 ４点
Well, excuse me for getting a four!
４点で悪かったな！
誰もが お前らみたいに
頭いいと思うなよ！
Not everyone's as smart as you!
Yep, that's right.
（天津）はい そのとおりだよ
It's the effort that counts.
大事なのは努力
Work hard, Kaizaki-kun.
頑張りましょう 海崎君
あっ はい
O-Okay.
Same to the rest of you.
（天津）他のみんなもね
（生徒たち）はーい
Right.
I could tutor you, if you like.
（大神）俺でよければ教えるけど？
（海崎）えっ？
余計なお世話ってんなら
あれだけど—
Sorry if I'm being too nosy,
but with those scores, who knows
when you'll escape the make-up loop?
その点じゃ いつ 再試ループ
抜けられるか 怪しくない？
I-I'm not sure if I should
feel insulted or not!
（海崎）くっ 屈辱と複雑…
Um!
（小野屋(おのや)）あの！
（海崎）ん？
（小野屋）
それ あたしも一緒にいいかな？
Could I get in on that?
Uh, Onoya-san?
ええと… 小野屋さん
You failed?
赤点あったの？
Yeah.
（小野屋）うん 全部
All of them.
Another complete failure!
（海崎）全滅が ここにも！
Oh, and...
しかも…
（小野屋）えへ へへへ えへ…
（大神）あ… はは…
Kaizaki-kun.
（小野屋）海崎君
（海崎）ん？
Headed for the cafeteria?
もしかして 学食？
お昼 一緒に食べない？
Wanna eat lunch together?
えっ？ えっと…
Uh...
What should I do at times like these?
（海崎）こういう事態は…
I'd be glad not to eat alone, but...
俺は ぼっち飯 回避できて
ありがたいけど—
At this age, a boy and
a girl eating together...
高校生が 男女２人で飯って—
Won't people make fun of her?
小野屋さん
からかわれたりしちゃうんじゃ…
（大神）俺も 一緒 いい？
（海崎）あっ
Can I join you?
We can get started on
our test prep planning!
せっかくだし
早速 再試対策でもする？
Oh, good idea! Thanks!
おお いいね！ 助かる！
（海崎）
ナイスだ チャラオーガ
Nice, Showga!
おっ 狩生も 一緒に行かない？
You coming, Kariu?
I'm eating with Honoka...
あたし ほのか…
With Tamarai-san.
玉来(たまらい)さんと食べるから
Oh, from the volleyball team?
（大神）おお バレー部の
Shame.
残念
あっ 俺 職員室行って
シルバーピン もらってから行く
I'm gonna swing by the
staff room for the silver pin.
You know where the cafeteria is?
２人とも 学食の場所 分かる？
うん 席取っとくね
Yep. We'll grab seats.
What the heck is a silver pin?
シルバーピンって何だっけ？
えっとね 確か 学級委員の印
Uh, I think it's...
the symbol of the class rep.
（海崎）へえ
Bread
Noodles
Sets/Bowls
Register
お待たせ
Thanks for waiting!
Say, you and Kariu-san
seem awfully close.
（小野屋）ねえ 大神君と
狩生さんって仲よさそうだけど—
Is she, like, your girlfriend?
狩生さんは
大神君の彼女さん… なのかな？
She came right out and asked him.
（海崎）
随分 ズバッと言ったな
でも…
But...
実は 俺も そうじゃないかって
思ってたんだよね
I was actually wondering the same thing.
Come on. Fess up.
（小野屋･海崎）
どうなの？ その辺
ちっ 違うよ
何で そんな勘違い
N-No.
What gave you that idea?
You're not dating?
違うのかよ
（小野屋）うーん 人間観察には
自信あったんだけどなあ
And here I thought I read people better.
あっ じゃあ もう一つ 質問
One other question, then.
彼女さんじゃないとしたら
その おそろいのピアスは 何？
If she's not your girlfriend,
what's with the matching earrings?
あっ？ ピアス？
Earrings?
よく気づいたね そんなとこ
Wow, you actually noticed that?
えへへ
これさあ 俺が１年の時…
Well, in first year...
兄ちゃんに 無理やり開けられてさ
My brother insisted on piercing my ear.
It hurt so much,
I didn't let him do the other ear.
痛くて もう
片耳で嫌になっちゃったから—
So the other half of this pair
is gonna go unused. Want it?
同じの １個余ってんだけど
いる？
そんな 自分が嫌になったものを
よくも 人に…
Are you seriously trying to fob it off on me
because you don't like it?
（大神）へへへへへ
だよねー はははははっ
Figures.
I'll take it.
（狩生）いる
（大神）えっ？
It's free, right?
（狩生）
くれるってんなら もらっとく
でも 狩生 部活もしてるのに
But you play volleyball...
（狩生）何なの!?
What's with you?
Are you giving it to me or not?
Make up your mind!
くれるの？ くれないの？
はっきりしなさいよ！
（大神）あああげます どうぞ！
I am! Here!
Jeez.
まったく しょうがないんだから
Since you insist...
I'll gratefully accept it.
もらってあげる
And she came in the very next day
with her ear pierced! Hilarious, right?
結局 次の日に
もう 開けてきてんの
ウケるよねえ
まあ そんな感じで
Anyway, that's all there is to it.
“付き合ってるの？”なんて
それ 聞いたら—
If you asked her if we were dating,
Kariu would go berserk!
狩生 ブチ切れるよ
（小野屋･海崎）はあー…
（大神）えっ 何？
Huh? What?
He might be book smart,
いくら お勉強ができても—
健全な高校男子として
どうなんですかねえ？ あれ
but he's the furthest thing from
an exemplary high school boy, huh?
いや まったく
イケメンの無駄遣い
Seriously. Total waste of a handsome face.
狩生さん かわいそう
I feel sorry for Kariu-san.
（海崎）かっわいそう
（大神）何で!?
Very sorry.
Why?
You should read more modern lit.
もっと 現代文 勉強したら？
登場人物の心情を
読み取るような問題を—
Focus your studies on comprehending
the emotions of the characters.
重点的にするといいかもよ
あれ？ えっ？
何で 俺が 指導受けてんの？
Wait, what? Why am I
being assigned homework?
Sorry, we can't.
Can't we please work it out?
ねえ 再試の話は？
What happened to prepping
for the make-ups?
Oh, dear.
（海崎）あっ
（日代）お願いします
Please.
（海崎）大神と同じ
シルバーピンの子だ
Oh, it's the other class rep.
Nothing I can do.
What's she doing?
何してんだ？
Looks like they're arguing.
なんか もめてるっぽい
I'll go see why.
（海崎）ちょい見てくる
（小野屋）えっ？
分かりました
今すぐ 職員室に行ってきます
Very well.
I'll go to the staff room
and be right back.
（海崎）
日代さん どうしたの？
What's wrong, Hishiro-san?
４点の人
It's the guy who got a four.
Don't mention that...
点言うのは やめて
The cigarettes guy, then?
では タバコの人
That's what you remember?
その覚え方 つらい
すみません
強烈だったので つい
Sorry. It left quite the impression.
A-Anyway, are you in trouble?
そ それより 何かトラブル？
I didn't bring any money out of habit.
いつもの癖で
お金を持ってこなかったんです
（日代）“シルバーピンを
取りに行くので—”
I said to wait while I got the silver pin,
Students with silver pins are to state their name and class every time.
And please wait in line like the others.
- Cafeteria Head
“待っていてください”と
言ったのですが—
“作ってしまったラーメンは
どうするのか”と
but they'd already made the ramen, so...
Help, I need an interpreter!
（海崎）
誰か 通訳してくれ
えっと つまり—
Um, so...
Basically, you forgot your money
and can't buy lunch?
お金忘れちゃって
昼が食えなくて困ってるってこと？
I didn't forget it.
忘れたんじゃありません
持ってこなかったんです
I just didn't bring any.
同じだろ
Same thing.
Hishiro-san!
日代さん
はい 貸すよ
Here.
Borrow this.
Pay me back whenever.
返してくれるのは いつでもいいし
I can't take that much.
（日代）こんなにもらえません
（海崎）はっ？
300円もあれば 大体のメニュー
食べられますし—
Most things here don't cost
more than 300 yen.
And I think 1,000 yen is a pretty
large sum for a high schooler.
高校生にとって 1000円って
結構 大きいと思うんですけど
それを こんなに軽く貸せるなんて
なんていうか…
How can you lend me
that much money so casually?
It's like...
...you're a grown-up.
大人ですね
I-It's fine!
いっ いいんだよ！
今日は たまたま多く持ってるの
I just happen
to have extra today! Here!
ほら！
（海崎）うわあっ！
とっさのこととはいえ—
It was an impulse,
but I just took a high school girl's hand!
ＪＫの手を
思いっ切り 握ってしまったーっ！
Then I'll take you up on your kind offer.
（日代）では すみません
お言葉に甘えて
Thank you.
ありがとうございます
I'll pay you back tomorrow.
明日 必ず返します
What am I getting worked up about?
（海崎）何だよ
何 ハッとしてんだ 俺！
She's in high school!
相手は 女子高生だぞ
No way!
ありえないから
（小野屋）やりますねえ
Smooth.
What?
（海崎）何だよ
（大神）カッコイイ！
Very cool.
Though you're not at all book smart.
勉強はできないけど
嫌な言い方するな
Knock that off!
She forgot her lunch money,
so I loaned her some.
昼飯代 忘れたって言うから
貸しただけだ
Last year's best student
is a bit of a ditz, huh?
学年１位なのに
意外と抜けてんのな
Nah, it's probably just because
she doesn't have her silver pin yet.
いや それ シルバーピン
まだ着けてなかったからじゃない？
はい？ 何でシルバーピン？
Why her silver pin?
When you've got this,
you can eat here for free.
（大神）これ 着けてると
学食 タダになんだよね
（海崎）マジで？
For real?
We also get commute allowance,
tuition exemption, and all sorts of perks.
他にも 交通費支給とか
学費免除とか 特典がついてくんの
何だ それ
すげえ お得
Whoa, that's pretty sweet.
But we'll never even
get a sniff of all that.
あたしたちには関係ないけどね
Oh, I get it now!
あっ 分かった
Kariu was trying for the silver pin—
狩生も シルバーピン目当てで
頑張ってたのか
（海崎･小野屋）それはない
No, she wasn't.
Onoya-san, you're harsh.
（大神）小野屋さん 厳しいな
（小野屋）ふふっ “杏(あん)”でいいよ
Call me An.
Really?
ああ ほんと？
じゃあ “杏ちゃん”で
Then, An-chan.
俺のことも
“カズ君”とかでいいよ
Feel free to call me Kazu-kun—
ううん “大神君”でいい
呼びやすいし
I'll stick with Oga-kun. It's easier.
Wh-What are you thinking?
ばっ… 何 考えてんだ！
学校で携帯！ 没収されるぞ
A cell phone at school?!
They'll confiscate it!
（小野屋）え？ 校則読んだけど
別に禁止じゃなかったよ
I read the school rules.
They aren't banned.
授業中は さすがに
マナーモードか電源オフだけどな
Gotta keep 'em off or
on vibrate in class, though.
えっ そう… なの？
What? Really?
Can I get your number?
（小野屋）携帯 聞いてもいい？
いいよー
Sure.
（海崎）俺の時代は 持ち込みすら
禁止で １か月 没収だったぞ
In my day, if you brought one in,
they'd take it for a month!
今って もう 怒られもしねえの？
They don't even yell at you now?!
Arata-kun, what's yours?
新太(あらた)君も教えて？
ああ… おう
You should call me An, too.
（小野屋）
新太君も “杏”でいいからね
Sure. An, then.
うん じゃあ “杏”で
すげえサラッと
呼び捨てたんですけど
Whoa! You just dropped the
honorific like it was nothing!
You're surprisingly good with girls.
新太の 思わぬ女慣れに驚いている
は？ 普通だろ
I'm normal.
（小野屋）
意外と純情なんだね 大神君
You're just weirdly naive, Oga-kun.
Apology Letter
（海崎）反省文 書くには
書いたけど こんなんでいいのか？
An apology letter...
I wrote something, but is it good enough?
I have written plenty
of these for work, but...
始末書なら 何遍も書いてるしな
The 1,000 yen,
1000円の
score of four,
（日代）４点の
（海崎）うっ！
and cigarette guy.
（日代）あと タバコの人
（海崎）うっ！
Seriously, don't remember me like that!
だから その覚え方！
Sorry. I couldn't recall your name.
すみません
お名前が思い出せなかったので
頭いいのに？
But you're smart.
（日代）それとこれとは
別だと思います
I think that's unrelated.
海崎です 海崎新太
It's Kaizaki.
Kaizaki Arata.
海崎新太
I've memorized it. I'm Hishiro...
覚えました 私は日代…
Um, why do you know my name?
そういえば そちらは なぜ
私の名前を？
I think you used it at lunch, too.
お昼の時
呼ばれた気がするんですが
昨日 自己紹介やったし—
We did introductions yesterday,
今朝のホームルームでも
紹介されてたろ
and you were introduced in
this morning's homeroom, too.
（日代）それだけで？
That's all you needed?
バカなのに？
But you're dumb.
Hey! That's going too far!
おい！ 言いすぎ！
思ってること 口に出しすぎ！
Don't say everything you think!
すみません
思ってても もう言いません
I apologize. I won't say it anymore,
even if that's what I think.
Oh, come on.
Staff Room
By the way, what were
you doing in the staff room?
ところで 何してたの？
職員室で
Oh, did you get in trouble, too?
あっ そっちも 何かやらかして
呼び出しとか？
それ 本気で言ってます？
Do you actually mean that?
すみません 冗談です
Sorry. That was a joke.
I came to pick up my silver pin.
（日代）
シルバーピンを受け取りに
あと テストで １か所
分からない所があったので—
Also, there was something
I didn't understand on the tests,
質問していたんです
so I asked about it.
へえ さすが まじめだな
Whoa. You sure are serious.
Am I a serious, boring girl?
（日代）まじめで
つまらない女でしょうか？
いや 別に
No, that's not it.
I heard you topped the grade last year,
so I just thought, "No wonder."
学年１位だって聞いたから
さすがだなーって思っただけで…
Sorry if I offended you.
気に障ったら ごめん
No, I should be the one apologizing.
（日代）
いえ こちらこそ すみません
そっ そういえば
何で 俺に敬語なの？
B-By the way, why do you
speak so formally to me?
もしかして 俺のこと
不良だとか 怖いとか思ってる？
Do you think I'm a delinquent
or scary or something?
I sure hope that's the case,
（海崎）だったら まだいいけど
はっきり年上に思われてるみたいで
心臓に悪いんだよ
because it feels like she thinks I'm older,
and that's giving me heart attacks.
昼 あんなこと言われたし
She said as much at lunch.
大人ですね
You're grown-up.
（日代）別に
Not really.
This is how I talk to everyone.
誰にでも こうなので
気にしないでください
Don't worry about it.
そうなんだ
Is that so?
Does that make me unapproachable?
（日代）とっつきにくいですか？
（海崎）え？
People tell me that a lot.
昔から よく言われてきました
この年になっても
親しい友人の１人もいませんし
Even at this age,
I don't have any close friends.
I never thought that was a problem,
別に それでも問題ないと思って
生きてきたんですが—
世の中 そうはいかないことも
多いらしくて
but apparently society does.
変わらなきゃと
思いつつ—
I keep thinking I need to change,
何をどうしたらいいのか
全く分からないんです
but I have no idea where to begin.
参考までに
教えてもらえませんか？
It would help if you could tell me honestly.
Am I really unapproachable?
やっぱり 私—
とっつきにくいんで
しょうか？
Frankly speaking, yeah.
（海崎）まあ 正直
（日代）グサッ
But I also feel like
you'd be worth getting to know.
でも 話せば面白い子なんだろうな
って感じもしてる
I dunno, maybe try smiling a little more?
もっと 普段からニコニコしてりゃ
いいんじゃねえかな
Smiling?
Like this?
こうですか？
You're kidding.
（海崎）うそだろ
（日代）今 引きましたよね
You just freaked out.
えっ！ いや ごめん
S-Sorry, it just wasn't
what I was expecting.
ちょっと 思ってたのと
違う感じのが来たから
（日代）じゃあ こうですか？
Then... like this?
（海崎）
いや さっきと変わってない！
No, that's the same!
やめよう！
笑顔作戦 やめよう！
No more! Abandon the smile strategy!
友達じゃなくて 敵作るわ
You'll make enemies, not friends!
If I can't even manage a polite smile,
愛想笑いのひとつも
できないなんて—
社会に出たら
きっと 困りますよね
I'll be in trouble in the real world.
Well, you don't have to rush things.
まあ 焦らなくても 友達くらい
自然とできてくもんだって
You'll make friends in time, I'm sure.
そう思っていた時期が
私にもありました
I thought I would, once.
（海崎）地雷踏んだ
Did I put my foot in it?
Oh, but I'm the same.
ああ でも 俺も同じだ
The future I assumed I would have
当たり前に
そうなると思ってた未来は—
never came to me.
自然になんて 来なかった
Of course I'd rush things.
（日代）焦りもしますよ
This year is my last chance.
もう 今年が最後ですもん
Oh, right.
（海崎）そっか ３年だもんな
We're third years.
ん… ってか ごめん
引き止めちゃって
Oh, sorry.
Kept you talking.
We'd better get home.
帰んないとな
Um!
（日代）あの！
（海崎）ん？
携帯を—
Can I have...
...your phone?
くれませんか？
Huh?
なん… 携帯 くれ？
Can you have... my phone?
I-I'm not sure how to respond to
this sudden attempt to mug me.
とっ 突然のカツアゲに
超戸惑っているんですが
（日代）違います
That's not it.
はあ… 足りない言葉くらい
補完してください
Fill in the blanks, please.
はい!?
Excuse me?
つまり だから…
Basically,
I mean...
携帯の番号を教えてくれませんかと
言っているんです
I want to know your phone number.
I'm saying I want to be your friend.
あなたと 友達になりたいと
言っているんです
I'm trying to take the first step
toward not being a friendless loner.
友達ゼロの ぼっち女が—
何とか 一歩
踏み出してみたところなんです
Please.
それぐらい 読み取ってください
Figure that much out.
ほんと バカですね
You really are dumb.
Sorry for not guessing all that.
んん… そりゃ
察せずに すみませんでした
But when you put it that clearly,
でも そういうふうに
ちゃんと言葉にすれば—
it won't be misunderstood, and I doubt
anyone would turn you down.
誤解なく伝わるし
拒否るやつも いねえと思うよ
Well said.
よく言えました
Don't treat me like an idiot, idiot.
バカが バカにしないでください
（海崎）
だから バカから離れよう！
Would you drop the insults
about my intelligence already?!
ってか お願い 離れて！
海崎さんも
話してみると 面白い人ですね
You also seem like someone
worth getting to know.
（海崎）なーんだ
ちゃんと笑えるじゃん
Would you look at that?
You can smile.
I see. For better or worse,
she's an utterly straightforward girl.
（海崎）そっか
よくも悪くも正直な子なんだな
（海崎）1000円 貸した時も
普通に笑えてたよ
You smiled when I loaned you
that 1,000 yen, too.
I did?
ほんとですか？ へへ…
（海崎）ああ だから
無理に笑おうとしなくていいって！
Ah, but don't try and force it!
Math's the killer.
やっぱ 問題は数学か
It's especially easy to
get hooked at your age!
10代は特に
依存症になりやすいの
やめられないんだよ？
You won't be able to quit!
Yoake
Call
（夜明）はい ええ
Yes... yeah...
Cigarettes?
タバコですか？
Well, only your exterior looks young,
それなら あくまで 見た目が
高校生に戻っているだけなので—
so that's not a problem.
問題はありません
Oh, okay.
そっか
（夜明）ただ その姿のままでは
買うことは難しいでしょうけどね
But you'll probably find it hard to
buy them with your appearance.
（夜明）いっそ 禁煙されたら
いかがですか？
May be a good time to quit!
においとか
どうしても しちゃいますからね
Hard to shake the smell, after all.
You just got Hishiro-san to smile.
（夜明）せっかく
日代さんに笑ってもらえたのに—
Can't have her turning against you!
嫌われちゃ 元も子もないでしょ？
What? You were watch—
なっ！ おまっ 見て！
（夜明）
ああいう子が お好みなんですか？
Is she your type?
何言ってんだ お前！
What the hell?!
仲よくしてあげてください
Be nice to her.
去年 同じクラスだったんですが
彼女 ずっと１人みたいだったので
I was in the same class with her last year,
and she was alone the whole time.
But, like I told you from the start,
ただ 最初にお話ししたとおり—
after your one-year ReLIFE period is over,
１年たって
リライフ期間が終了した後—
クラスメイトや教師 海崎さんに
関わった すべての人から—
classmates, teachers, and anyone
you dealt with will forget about you.
海崎さんの記憶は消えます
This is because 17-year-old
Kaizaki does not exist.
これは 17歳の海崎さん
という人間は—
この世には
存在しないためです
But your own memories
will remain, so don't worry.
でも 海崎さん自身の記憶は
そのままですから—
ご安心ください
そこ 消してしまったら—
If we erased those,
there'd be no point to the ReLIFE.
リライフの意味が
なくなってしまいます
However...
ただし…
If I tell anyone else about ReLIFE,
このリライフのことを
他言した場合は 実験は即終了
the experiment will end immediately.
And you'll wipe my memories and throw me out?
俺も 記憶を消されて
放り出される
Exactly.
そのとおりです
You can't talk about this. Ever.
一切 他言は許されません
If you do, you'll find yourself wondering
もし そうなったら
まーったく記憶のないまま—
気づいたら28歳になっちゃった
なんてことに なりうるわけです
how you got to be twenty-eight
without remembering it.
So be careful, okay?
くれぐれも お気をつけくださいね
Hishiro Chizuru
New message
Close View
Hishiro Chizuru
Hello. This is Hishiro.
Thank you very much for today.
I promise to return the 1,000 yen tomorrow.
（日代）“お借りした千円は
明日 必ずお返し致します”
“何卒 よろしくお願い致します”
I look forward to knowing you further.
（海崎）業務連絡かよ！
Is this a business e-mail?!
おお スタンプ！ 意外
Whoa, a sticker!
Surprising.
Likewise.
（海崎）“こっちこそ LIME(ライム)
聞いてもらえて 嬉しかった”
Thanks for adding me on LIME.
“ありがと”
By the way, this sticker of the sorry cat...
“ところで この
「バツネコ」スタンプ…”
It kinda looks like you.
Uh oh, she's gonna get mad at me
for saying dumb crap again.
（海崎）やべっ
これ また“バカなこと言うな”
って怒られるかな
I didn't mean it in a bad way!
別に 悪い意味で
言ったつもりじゃないんだけど
I dunno if she'll get that...
こういうの 通じなさそう
Meow.
（海崎）ブフッ
（海崎）なっ… まさかの返し
I did not see that coming!
Yeah, she's pretty weird.
And adorable!
やっぱ あの子 ちょっと変だわ
何これ かわいい
（海崎）んっ ん〜 ハァ
〜♪
NEXT EPISODE
（大神）
日代さん お昼はラーメン？
Having ramen for lunch, Hishiro-san?
（日代）学食では
とんこつラーメン一択です
I only eat tonkotsu ramen
at the cafeteria.
（大神）えっ 毎回同じ？
What, every day?
（日代）はい ですが 先日
シルバーピンがなくて—
That's right. But the other day,
I ran into some trouble
due to not having my silver pin.
大変な目に遭いました
You're Old Now
大神さんも お気をつけください
You should be careful, Oga-san.
（大神）オッケー
Okay!